A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37 (A2012) FA472
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2012.085: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 1990-2007; AC_2012_085; 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes
  - Food Security (FS), 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - Tropical Soil Biology and Fertility Programme (Kenya) - Socio-Economic Assessment of Cattle Manure for Soil Fertility Management in Zimbabwe 2000 FS 144, 2000-2003 (Box R3986)
    - Vicente Guerrero Rural Development Project (Mexico) - Farmer-Led Agricultural Technology Dissemination 2000 FS 147, 2000-2004 (Box R3986)
    - University of Zimbabwe - Self Nodulating Soyabeans 2000 FS 149, 1995-2004 (Box R3986)
    - University of Nairobi (Kenya) - Training in Agricultural Sciences; Maize-Pigeonpea Intercropping Systems 2000 FS 151, 1999-2003 (Box R3986)
    - University of Pretoria (South Africa) - Biotechnology and Smallholder Farmers 2000 FS 168, 2000-2004 (Box R3986)
    - Network for Studies on Rural Development - Farmer Field Schools 2000 FS 173, 2000-2002 (Box R3986)
    - National Agricultural Research Information (Uganda) - Genetic Improvement of Beans 2000 FS 174, 2000-2004 (Box R3986)
    - Institute of Agricultural Sciences of Rwanda - Genetic Improvement of Bush and Climbing Beans 2000 FS 177, 2000-2004 (Box R3986)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (Nigeria) - Publication of Cowpea Conference Proceedings 2000 FS 181, 2000-2001 (Box R3986)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Field Training; Biometrics Curriculum Reform 2001 FS 009, 2000-2003 (Box R3986)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Field Training; Productivity of Cereal Legume Intercrops 2001 FS 020, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Moi University (Kenya) - Field Training; Soil Fertility Management Technologies 2001 FS 025, 2000-2003 (Box R3987)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (Mexico) - Striga Hermonthica Resistance and Maize 2001 FS 027, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Local Area Network to Improve Internet Access 2001 FS 028, 2000-2002 (Box R3987)
    - University of Nairobi (Kenya) - Resistance to Angular Leaf Sopt in Beans 2001 FS 030, 2000-2003 (Box R3987)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Documentation and Dissemination of Forum Research and Development 2001 FS 034, 2001-2003 (Box R3987)
    - Basis for Integrated Development Initiatives (Kenya) - Seed Production/Promotion/Distribution Project 2001 FS 036, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - University or Malawi - Field Training; Gray Leaf Spot Maize Disease 2001 FS 061, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Malawi - Agriculture and Irrigation (Ministry of) - Training in Geographic Information Systems 2001 FS 067, 2000-2005 (Box R3987)
    - University of Nairobi (Kenya) - Field Training; Bean Root Fungus 2001 FS 049, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Crop Science of America - Plant Growth Symposium 2001 FS 071, 2001-2005 (Box R3987)
    - Digital Imaging and Spectral Techniques: Applications to Precision Agriculture and Crop Physiology. ASA Special Publication Number 66. 2001 FS 071 (A12), 2012:085:005 (Box R3987)
    - Muranga, Florence - Processed Bananas for Nutrition Improvement in Uganda 2001 FS 082, 1999-2001 (Box R3987)
    - Kenyatta University (Kenya) - Field Training; Soil Organic Matter and Crop Growth 2001 FS 091, 2001-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Rodale Institute - Global Young Farmers Leadership Development Program in Asia, Africa and Latin America 2001 FS 093, 2001-2003 (Box R3987)
    - Zimbabwe Institute of permaculture - Agroecology Training Course 2001 FS 112, 2001-2005 (Box R3987)
    - (Food Security) - Biotechnoogy and Maize Streak Virus Resistance in East Africa 2001 FS 114, 2001-2002 (Box R3987)
    - University of Zimbabwe - Field Training; Striga Asiatica Control 2001 FS 118, 2000-2004 (Box R3987)
    - Mugendi, Daniel Njiru - Agroforestry for Enhanced Soil Productivity in Kenya 2001 FS 128, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Forum Internal Review Committee 2001 FS 137, 1999-2003 (Box R3988)
    - Ssebuliva, James M. - African Career Award 2001 FS 141, 2001-2005 (Box R3988)
    - University of Malawi - Farmer-Led Schools for Improving Food Security 2001 FS 144, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Field Training; Resource-Use Plans for Peri-Urban Farming, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Field Training; Potato Production Technologies in the Highlands 2001 FS 149, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Field Training; Animal Draft Power Technologies, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Institute of Biotechnology - National Center for Natural Science and Technology (Vietnam) - Genetic Mapping of Drought Tolerance Traits; Breeding of Upland Rices 2001 FS 164, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Kenya Agricultural Research Institute - Participatory Monitoring and Evaluation Workshop 2001 FS 175, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Mapfuno, Paul - African Career Award 2001 FS 179, 2000-2005 (Box R3988)
    - Kenyatta University (Kenya) - Management of Fusarium Moniliforme in Maize 2001 FS 181, 1999-2005 (Box R3988)
    - Kenya Agricultural Research Institute - Proceedings of 18th Soil Science Society of East Africa Conference 2001 FS 184, 2001-2004 (Box R3988)
    - Sserunkuuma, Dick - ACA: Feed Resources as a Supplement to Private Natural Pastures in Uganda 2002 FS 004, 1997-2003 (Box R3988)
    - Ogol, Callistus K.P. - ACA: Natural Resource and Biodiversity on Mfangano Island 2002 FS 016, 1999-2005 (Box R3988)
    - African Centre for Technology Studies (Kenya) - Roundtable on Plant Genetic Resources in Africa 2002 FS 031, 2002-2003 (Box R3988)